<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Programming Lab</title>
    <link>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Programming Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:27:51 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Blog With Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/docs/setting_up_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/docs/setting_up_blog/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Blog With Github Pages and Hugo#Hugo is a static site generator that lets us create sites very fast.
Install hugo from installation page of hugo. Follow appropriate steps need to instal it.
We also need git to be installed. Make sure git is setup in the system.
Generating new site with hugo
hugo new site &amp;lt;site_name&amp;gt; Example:
hugo new site sample-site cd sample-site Adding theme. We can add any theme we want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stopped Using Notion</title>
      <link>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/docs/stopped_using_notion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/docs/stopped_using_notion/</guid>
      <description>Why I stopped using Notion for everything#Notion is an all in one note taking app. It started as so, but I think now it has growen more than that. I was a notion fanatic, had my complete life setup in notion. My daily task, bookmark of websites, TV-shows, books and much more.
I started using notion to organize thing in my life, whatever I did, used to update that in notion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming Lab</title>
      <link>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/posts/programming_lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:27:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/posts/programming_lab/</guid>
      <description>Programming Lab#I wanted this to reflect me as a professional, where I could attract some potential people who would pay for my work, but later thought, I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do that and here it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;
DISCLAIMER#NOTE : ALL THESE ARE MY OWN OPNION AND IN NO WAY IT REFLECT ANY OF MY SURROUNDING PEOPLE INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO MY FAMILY, FRIENDS, EMPLOYERS, EMPLOYEES or ANYONE ELSE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jsx as Template</title>
      <link>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/posts/jsx_as_template/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 06:19:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://abhishekgowda28.github.io/posts/jsx_as_template/</guid>
      <description>JSX as a templating language#If you are doing web development in react, you would know what JSX is. If not go look it up, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to explain. And if your using typescript in web development it&amp;rsquo;s tsx.
This is how a sample JSX looks like
const SampleJsx = () =&amp;gt; { return ( &amp;lt;div&amp;gt; &amp;lt;div&amp;gt;SampleJSX&amp;lt;div&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/div&amp;gt; ) } And this is how a regular XML looks like</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
